Hamidreza Moaddeli

 \square +98 917 7012434 • \square hamidreza.moaddeli@gmail.com • \square moaddeli.github.io in Moaddeli • \square @moaddelin r

Professional Summary

As a Principal Machine Learning Engineer with over 6 years of experience, I have led the development and deployment of machine learning models across various domains, particularly in medical applications. My expertise spans various fields, including natural language processing, computer vision, and Multimodal data. My passion for continuous learning and improvement keeps me at the forefront of the rapidly evolving Al landscape, and I am committed to delivering high-impact results that contribute to organizational growth and excellence.

Professional Experience

Work Experience.....

KroniKare Pte Ltd Melbourne ,Australia

Senior Machine Learning Engineer (Remote)

Apr.2022-Present

- Designing, implementing and deploying deep learning models for segmentation and measuring different areas of chronic wounds.
- Design, implementation, and deployment of deep learning models for the detection of complications using multispectral images of the wound of the patient.

Artin Shiraz,Iran

Machine Learning Engineer

Jul.2020–Mar.2022

- Design and deploying deep learning models for segmentation and measuring different areas Brain Tumors using Multimodal MRI scans

Freelance Shiraz, Iran

Freelance Python Developer/Data Scientist

Sept.2014-Jul.2020

- Developing software for scientific computing and data analysis using SciPy Stack (SciPy, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas and IPython Notebook.) and Mysql and SQLite DataBases.

Pars Hassas Co. Shiraz,Irai

Senior Automation Software Engineer

Dec.2010-Sept.2014

- Designing and implementing HMI softwares, logic programs, loop controls and network configuration for multiple small to large projects including Yokogawa DCSs, Siemens PLCs and HIMA ESDs.
- Worked as a main developer for the project "Design and implementation a Telemetry system for water supply network of Shiraz city"

Pars Hassas Co. Shiraz,Iran

Automation Software Engineer

Sept.2008-Dec.2010

- Worked as a main developer for the project "Design and development of a new monitoring system for PSA Unit of Bandar-Abass Oil Refinery".

Pars Hassas Co. Shiraz,Iran

Part-time Automation Software Programmer

Sept.2005-Sept.2008

Teaching Experience.....

Teaching Assistant

Azad University of Shiraz

Shiraz, Iran

Lecturer 2009–2010

Courses: Assembly Language Programming, Discrete Mathematics, Data Storage and Retrieval and Artificial Intelligence

Faculty of Engineering Shahid Bahonar Shiraz

Shiraz,Iran Fall 2005

Lecturer

Courses Computer Craphics Lab and Fundamentals of Wah

Courses: Computer Graphics Lab and Fundamentals of Web

Shiraz, Iran

Shiraz University

2003–2006

Courses: Fundamentals Of Programming (Python Programming), Discrete Mathematics, File Structures, Artificial Intelligence, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, Operating Systems Lab, Operating Systems and Advanced Mathematics in Computer Engineering

Research Experience.

Shiraz University Shiraz, Iran

Part-time Research Assistant, Advisor: Dr. F. Khunjush

Sept.2009-May.2012

Research focused on:

- Studying different performance analysis and modeling methods for GPU Architectures.
- Employing Machine learning and Statistical techniques in Performance optimization and modeling (specifically for many-core architectures).

Technical and Personal skills

General Skills: Excellent communication and presentation skills, Problem solving skills with strong background in mathematics, Collaboration and teamwork skills, Self-motivated learner.

Programming Languages: Python, C/C++, Octave, R, Java, JavaScript, Angular, HTML

Data Science and Machine Learning: Python SciPy Stack (SciPy, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, scikit-learn), Spark,

TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Programming Tools: CUDA, MPI, OpenMP, Git

Systems: Windows, Linux/Unix, Embedded Linux systems, and Container(Docker)

Language Proficiency: Fluent in English, Native in persian

Education

Shiraz University Shiraz, Iran

M.Sc. in Computer Engineering, Software Engineering Major, GPA: 17.67/20.0 2005–2008

Master thesis: "Design and Implementation of a Prototype for Resource Reservation Mechanism in Grid Environment"

supervisor: Dr. GH.Dastghaiby Fard

Shiraz University Shiraz, Iran

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering, Software Engineering Major, GPA: 17.66/20.0

Final year project: "Design and Implementation of NACHOS in Python Programming Language"

supervisor: Dr. A. Towhidi

Honors and Awards

 \circ Ranked 24^{th} among more than 400,000 participants in Iranian National University Entrance Exam (B.Sc.), 2000.

- o Singapore International Graduate Award (SINGA), A*STAR, Singapore, January 2013.
- o Ranked 1st place in B.Sc., Computer Science and Engineering Department at Shiraz University, 2005.
- o Ranked 78th in Iranian National M.Sc. University Entrance Exam (Software Engineering Track), 2005.
- \circ Ranked 31^{st} in Iranian National M.Sc. University Entrance Exam (Artificial Intelligence Track), 2004.
- \circ Ranked 52^{nd} in Iranian National M.Sc. University Entrance Exam (Computer Architecture Track), 2004.
- o 4-year Exceptional Talent Undergraduate Student Award (Academic-based), 2000-2004.
- o Member of Iranian Elite Foundation, 2008-present.

Selected Courses

Deep Learning Nanodegree Program: Udacity (Online Course), November 2017 Cohort

Big Data Analysis with Apache Spark: edX (Online Course), September 2016

Introduction to Apache Spark: edX (Online Course), September 2016

Distributed Machine Learning with Apache Spark: edX, August 2016

Big Data(a series of two courses): BerkeleyX-edX, August 2015

Scalable Machine Learning: edX (Online Course), August 2015

Verified Certificate: 100/100

XSeries Certificate: 100/100

Introduction to Big Data with Apache Spark: edX (Online Course), July 2015

Verified Certificate: 100/100

Verified Certificate: 100/100

Design and Analysis of Algorithms: Coursera (Online Course), Spring 2012, Stanford University

Verified Certificate: 100/100

100/100

Machine Learning: Coursera (Online Course), Fall 2011, Stanford University 400/400

Artificial Intelligence: Coursera (Online Course), Fall 2011, Stanford University 97.8/100(top 10%)

Publications and Presentations

- **H. Moaddeli**, G. Dastghaibyfard, and M. Moosavi, "Flexible advance reservation impact on backfilling scheduling strategies," in Grid and Cooperative Computing, 2008. GCC 08. Seventh International Conference on, Oct 2008, pp. 151–159.
- o H. Moaddeli, "Foundation Models", K. N. Toosi University of Technology, November 2024
- **H. Moaddeli**, "Al in Ophthalmology", Poostchi Ophthalmology Research Center, Department of Ophthalmology School of Medicine, Shiraz University of Medical Sciences, Shiraz, Iran, January 2020

2000-2005